<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_s_description">Pizzas description</string>
    <string name="diabola_description">Pizza alla Diavola, a pretty spicy pizza. Diavola contains spicy Italian salami,
                  peperoncino, which is a spicy pepper and even red chili flakes.
                  A devilish pizza that will leave water in your mouth!</string>
    <string name="funghi_description">Now that I’ve got the hang of making great pizza at home using cold-fermented
                 dough and baking it tender but crispy in 3 minutes on an aluminum plate,
                 it is time to make pizzas with different toppings. Mushrooms are always a favorite,
                 and the most important thing to get it right is to always sauté the mushrooms before putting them on a pizza.
                 When you bake the mushrooms raw, they will release a lot of liquid that will make your pizza soggy.
                 For additional flavor I like to sauté the mushrooms trifolati, with garlic and parsley.</string>
    <string name="capricciosa_description">The pizza capricious is the most classic Italian pizzas.
                And present in all menus of pizzerias. The customer undecided always end up ordering the pizza capricious,
                rich, abundant and imaginative, this pizza always manages to please everyone.</string>
    <string name="hawaii_description">Thin pizza bases
                140g tub pizza sauce
                200g light shaved ham
                1/4 pineapple, peeled, cut into 2cm pieces
                150g button mushrooms, finely sliced
                1 teaspoon dried mixed Italian herbs
                1 cup grated low-fat mozzarella cheese
                100g baby spinach, to serve</string>
    <string name="aglio_e_olio_description">Heat broiler with rack in top position
                place sheet of foil on rack below to catch any drips.
                Combine garlic, chile, and 1/4 cup oil in a small saucepan over low heat and cook until softened, about 4 minutes.
                Place crust on a baking sheet or pizza peel. Spread tomatoes over crust, leaving a 1/2” border.
                Scatter some garlic and chile over top, then drizzle with some of the infused oil. Slide pizza onto rack and broil,
                checking often, until crust is charred and blistered in spots, 6–8 minutes.
                Using a pair of tongs, remove pizza from oven; sprinkle with salt and red pepper flakes, drizzle with olive oil,
                and top with parsley</string>
    <string name="ai_frutti_di_mare_description">Ingredients:
                One 13 inch frying pan (Cast Iron, any size will really do).
                3 large cloves of garlic, sliced in half (you will later discard them)
                One pint of small cherry tomatoes
                2 teaspoons of salt
                1 teaspoon pepper
                1 teaspoon  hot red pepper (optional)
                2 tablespoons of olive oil
                1/2 cup of white wine (clams)
                1 additional tablespoon of olive oil to brush onto your dough
                6-8 jumbo shrimp, cleaned, leave the peeling on.   You will finish cleaning them before assembly on pizza
                1 pound clams (baby, small, little neck or of equal kind), fresh or frozen with shells if available in your area</string>
    <string name="al_prosciutto_description">INGREDIENTS :
                 150g buffalo mozzarella, or 4 bocconcini balls
                 Extra virgin olive oil, to drizzle
                 25g parmesan cheese, grated
                 8 slices prosciutto, torn
                 10 cherry tomatoes, halved
                 2 cups wild rocket leaves
                 Pizza dough
                 350g strong (baker\'s) flour, plus extra to dust
                 1 teaspoon caster sugar
                 7g packet dried instant yeast
                 2 tablespoons olive oil</string>
    <string name="quattro_stagioni_description">Our Readers Also Loved
                 Pizza Quattro Stagioni
                 Chocolate Lava Cake Crockpot Recipe
                 Pizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro Stagioni
                 Pizza Quattro Stagioni
                 Incredible Peach And Plum Dump Cake Recipe
                 Pizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro Stagioni
                 Pizza Quattro Stagioni
                 Aromatic Cherry Dump Cake Crockpot Recipe
                 Pizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro StagioniPizza Quattro Stagioni </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
</resources>
